[
    {
        "question": "Select angular directives",
        "options": [
            "ngFor",
            "init",
            "list",
            "ngIf"
        ],
        "type": "checkbox",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": [0,3]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Model in MVC?",
        "options": [
            "Model represents server side data.",
            "Model represents data stored in database.",
            "Model is the lowest level of the pattern responsible for maintaining data.",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How angular.module works?",
        "options": [
            "angular.module is used to create AngularJS modules along with its dependent modules.",
            "angular.module is primarily used to create application module.",
            "Both of the above.",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which file is responsible for startup of angular 2 project ?",
        "options": [
            "main.ts", "index.js", "app.ts", "angular.cli.json" 
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decorator used for configuring your module class?",
        "options": [
            "@NgModule", "@NgApp", "@NgAngular", "@NgConfigure"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Interpolation in angular 2 is done using",
        "options": [
            "{{}}", "{{|var}}", "{{{}}}", "!!!!"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is used for chaining multiple pipes in Angular",
        "options": [
           ":", "-", ",", "|"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following filter is used to convert input to all uppercase?",
        "options": [
            "upper", "uppercase", "toUpper", "none of the above"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a hook in Angular application life cycle.",
        "options": [
            "ngOnChanges", "ngOnInit", "ngAfterViewInit", "ngViewStart"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Angular is a?",
        "options": [
        ],
        "type": "text",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": "framework"
    }
]